[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who prompted the marketing of sliced bread in 1928?", "correct_answer": "W.E. Long", "incorrect_answers": ["Gustav Papendick", "Otto Rohwedder", "Herbert Dinklebrot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the term dutching mean when referring to chocolate?", "correct_answer": "Alkalizing the chocolate", "incorrect_answers": ["Hardening the chocolate", "Pulverizing the chocolate", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All arteries carry oxygenated blood from the heart to the rest of the body.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At weddings it is common for people to toast the bride or groom. The term toast originates from Italy where it was common to place a piece of bread in the bottom of a wine cup for flavor.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the title of the national anthem of Switzerland?", "correct_answer": "Swiss Psalm", "incorrect_answers": ["Swiss Vow", "Swiss Song", "Swiss Anthem"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "While muscle stimulation occurs during weight lifting and resistance exercises, muscle growth occurs later when the muscles are at rest.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Japanese words Mizaru, Kikazaru and Iwazaru, which embody the proverbial principle to see no evil, to hear no evil, and to speak no evil refer to what?", "correct_answer": "The three wise monkeys.", "incorrect_answers": ["The Japanese names for the Biblical characters Shadrack, Meshaxk, and Abendebego.", "None of these", "The names of the three diamonds in the Mitsubishi logo."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The iPhone is the only 3G phone.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these artists appears in the  Carmen: A Hip Hopera?", "correct_answer": "Bow Wow", "incorrect_answers": ["Chris Brown", "Soulja Boy", "Sean Kingston"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was written on the girls bathroom mirror according to the popular urban legend about the The Licked Hand?", "correct_answer": "Humans can lick too", "incorrect_answers": ["One down, two to go", "Dont look under the bed", "Come here doggie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The aorta carries deoxygenated blood from the heart to the rest of the body.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What head football coach makes a cameo in the movie Facing the Giants?", "correct_answer": "Mark Richt", "incorrect_answers": ["Bobby Johnson", "Jim Donnan", "Frank Beamer"]}]